Do you know about a vehicle
that is a small package with a big bang?  She
listens and moves on in the city traffic.  And
if you look carefully, you can also see a winged horse.
I am talking about i icer
model 2095 xt.  Along with 11,100 GBW, you get the
E474 engine which
generates 140 horsepower which gives you an
excellent torque of 400 Nm.
Amaster technology has been provided which will give
you excellent mileage in the car.
Apart from that, cruise control is also provided here.
Fuel coaching system is also provided.
You get a 12 volt charging
spot here.  So here you
also get a music system.
AC is also provided here.  Comfortable full cabin
seat is provided.  To buy such a budget friendly
small size and big car at a profit,
contact AB Motors.